Previously on Transformers Prime...
在上一集中
The download of the Iacon database may have been incomplete,
尽管下载到的铁堡数据不完整
but we now possess four sets of coordinates decoded by the ship.
但我们已经拥有了战舰所破译的四个坐标
If we are to have any hope of recovering the Iacon relics before the Decepticons do,
如果我们想赶在霸天虎之前得到铁堡的遗物
we must divide our resources.
我们就必须分头行动
Dispatching multiple squadrons will enable us to pursue all four coordinates simultaneously.
派出多支小队 同时前往这四个地点
Be on your guard, Bulkhead.
保持警惕 隔板
Ratchet, come here.
救护车 到这边来！
The Iacon database.
铁堡数据库
It's downloading into our mainframe.
它下载到我们的主机上来了！
Hahahahaha! Rafael, you are a genius!
哈哈哈！拉斐尔你真是个天才！
Bulkhead's coming through, Agent Fowler.
隔板回来了 福勒探员
I can't wait to share the news.
我等不及要分享这个消息了！
No!
不…！
Who is the fiercest among you?
谁是你们中的最强者？
There is no greater ferocity than Insecticon hive,
说到凶残 什么也不及一整窝的机器昆虫
but if you would to choose one among us...
但您一定要从我们中间挑一个的话…
... I am Hardshell.
…我是硬壳
You will retrieve something for me, Hardshell,
你去替我拿回一样东西 硬壳
and annihilate everything that gets in your way!
并消灭一切敢于阻挠你的人！
Divide and do not hesitate to conquer!
散开！迅速行动 踏上征途！
Miko and Jack will accompany Arcee and Bumblebee.
神子和杰克陪大黄蜂还有阿尔茜前往
Yes!
太好了！
Initiate transport...
开始传送
... and triangulate coordinates of the other three relics.
同时开始定位另外三组坐标
That was some trick, Miko.
这可不是远足 神子
You mean, swiping intel from right under Megatron's nose?
那从威震天鼻子底下扫描情报呢？
Just doing my part for team Prime!
我是领袖卫队的一员！
Oh, got to go Bulk!
哦 我得走了 小隔
I'll tell you all about it when we get back.
等我回来再跟你讲整个故事
Wait up!
等等我！
- Take care of her, Bee. - Take care of him, Miko.
- 照顾好她 小蜂 - 照顾好他 神子
Bulkhead, prepare for departure.
隔板 准备出发
You are headed for the equator.
你将前往赤道
I'll prep for tropical weather... wrecker style.
我去体会热带风情了 雷霆救援队来袭！
Rafael and Agent Fowler will be your communications and transportation hub.
拉斐尔和福勒探员负责联络和进行传送
I can't. That's cheeseburger!
我吃不下芝士汉堡包了 呃！
Communications, huh?
联络 嗯？
Be on your guard, Bulkhead.
保持警惕 隔板
Oh...
哦 哦！
Smells worse than a Decepticon barraks.
比霸天虎兵营还要难闻！
Fine place to hide a relic.
真是个藏遗物的好地方！
Base, I can't find any sight of the relic.
基地 我找不到任何遗物的信号
Can you reconfirm coordinates?
你能确定坐标吗？
Triangulating your position, Bulkhead.
正在测定你的位置 隔板
You're at the correct location.
你的位置没有错误
Oh... Need coffee...
哦 得来点咖啡
And the coordinates are wrong, 'cause there is nothing here.
那就是坐标错了 这里什么都没有…
But something's coming.
…不过有东西来了！
Leave it to Megatron to send a bug to do his dirty work.
威震天派只虫子来替他干见不得人的勾当
You know a thing or two of dirty work yourself, Wrecker.
你也不是什么清白的货色 救援队小子！
Do I know you?
我认识你吗？
I know your kind...
我认识你的同类
... as I have crossed more than a few Wreckers in my time.
因为我这辈子碾碎的救援队员已经数不清了
Now you see the thing about bugs your size.
瞧你这个大块头
They make a bigger mess when I smash them.
等我砸碎你时 得是多大的一块废铁！
Ratchet, the virus is coded.
救护车 病毒编写完成
Commencing upload.
开始上传
Raf, I have a bead on the relic.
拉夫 我猜到遗物的位置了
Raf is busy. I'll take it from here.
拉夫正忙 我来接手
Fowler? How was your beauty sleep?
福勒！睡得怎么样？
Fine. Jumped I finally got low respect from you.
很好 梦到你终于对我尊重点了
Keep dreaming.
继续做梦吧！
What's your status?
你的情况？
Came up empty to provided coordinates.
在坐标处一无所获
But I'm figuring old lava flow might have carried relic downhill.
但我猜想应该是早期的熔岩流把遗物带下了山
Wouldn't that just burn it up?
熔岩不会烧毁遗物吗？
This relic survived interstellar transport,
遗物能经受住星际旅行
I'm sure that can stand multi....
我相信它们禁得住岩浆…
... oh, scrap.
…哦 该死！
What is it?
怎么了？
I'm leaking Energon. Insecticon hit me hard.
我在漏能量 机器昆虫把我伤得不轻
Insecticon?
机器昆虫？
Probably not the gasket wheels.
大概垫片没有受损
Nothing to worry about.
没什么可担心的 相信我
The Wrecker left me alive.
他留了我一条命
The last mistake he will ever make.
这是致命的错误
There you are!
找到你了！
Got the lid off.
盖子打开了！
O-oh. Base... we have a problem.
啊哦 基地 我们有麻烦了
Bulkhead, what is it?
隔板 怎么了？
I found the relic. It's a cash of Energon.
我找到遗物了 是一个能量储存块
That's good, right?
那很好 不是吗？
No-no-no, not this kind.
不 不 不 不是这种好法
It's known as Tox-En.
它被称为毒能
Causes nausy and dizziness upon contact.
接触后会产生恶心和头晕
Prolong exposal weakens us to the point of paralysis.
长期暴露其中会使我们麻痹
And then... it snuffs out our sparks.
最终 熄灭我们的火种
Well, what do you talking to me for?
那还说这么多干嘛？
Get far away from that Tox-En. Prompto.
快远离那个毒能！
If it is as deadly as you say...
如果它真像传说的那般致命
... the 'Cons won't want it either.
虎子们也不会想得到它！
No, they'll want it even more.
不 他们十分想得到它
During the war for Cybertron.
在塞博特恩的战争中
Megatron figured out a way to refine raw Tox-En...
威震天找到一种提炼天然毒能的方法
... turning it to a weapon of mass destruction.
制作成一种大规模杀伤性武器
I witnessed when entire unit wiped out by the sickness.
我目睹了一整支部队因中毒而全军覆没
No way I can leave this stuff for 'Cons to find and abuse.
我绝不能把这东西留给虎子们用来为非作歹
So bring it back here.
那么把它带回来
Raf? Open a Ground Bridge.
拉夫？打开环陆桥
Forget it. Even if we had a safe place to store it...
不行 就算我们能找到安全的容器保存它
... the stuff's way too potently risky to exposing the rest of us...
这东西的潜在威胁也很大 不能冒险再让其他人接触它
I'll call you back.
啊 我等会儿再联系你
I gonna need to take care of this... Wrecker style.
我要用雷霆救援队的方式来处理这个东西
There.
嗯 在那里！
No! Wait!
不 等等！
Tox-En.
啊 毒能！
Wait, you're carying it?
什么 你带着它走？
I thought that stuff was toxic.
那东西不是有毒吗？
It is. But I needed to put some distance between me and the bugs.
是有毒 但是我需要与虫子们拉开距离
Well, what now?
好吧 那要怎么做？
I'm gonna get rid of this steaming pile the only way I can.
只有一个办法可以处理掉这堆冒气的东西
I'm gonna lob it into the volcano.
我要把它扔进火山
What about the insect problem?
那些昆虫怎么办？
This isn't my first time aluding an enemy patrol, you know.
知道吗 我对反侦查很有心得
Lord Megatron, the object we seek...
威震天陛下 我们要找的物品
It is Tox-En.
是毒能
Exactly how much is in your possession?
那你到底拿到了多少？
None, my lord. An Autobot...
一无所获 我的主人 一个汽车人…
Are you not the fiercest Insecticon?
你不是最强的机器昆虫吗？
Wait, you're moving away from the volcano?
等等 你在远离火山？
Exactly.
完全正确…
Below.
下边！
Yes.  The Wrecker leaks from his wounds.
没错… 从救援队那小子的伤口流下来的
Find him!
找到他！
You did the false trail, huh?
你留下了误导的踪迹 哈？
I once pulled that trick when I got separated...
我曾在敌人后方与部队走散时
... from my unit behind enemy lines.
也用过这招
When where you ever behind enemy lines?
你什么时候到过敌人后方？
I wasn't always a bot-sitter.
我以前可不是机器人保姆
Next you gonna tell me your mother doesn't tuck you in at night?
下次你该说你妈妈晚上没有帮你掖被子了
That's as basic training.
这可是基本训练
Training as what? A rodeo clown?
训练做什么？秀场小丑吗？
You was been way too muc time in monster truck rallies with Miko.
你浪费了太多时间去陪神子玩怪物卡车了
I was an army ranger.
我曾是一个游骑兵队员
We could wreck with the best of them.
我们干得不比任何人差
Who knew you and I are so much alike.
谁能想到我们如此相像
Rafael! Has Agent Fowler regained consciousness?
拉斐尔 福勒探员恢复知觉了吗？
Stand by, Bulkhead.
等一下 隔板
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
I'm here, Prime.
我在这儿 擎天柱
What's the situation?
你那边是什么情况？
I require access to a research facility at my current coordinates.
我需要进入一处考察站 就在我所在的位置
Let me make a call.
让我联系一下
The dirty job.
只有雷霆救援队员
That only a Wrecker can do.
干得了这样的脏活
C'mon!
来吧！
This is an emergency!
这是紧急情况
Our satellites have detected dangerous solar flare activity!
我们的卫星侦测到高危程度的太阳活动
I need that entire station evacuated immediately!
我需要那个基地里的所有人员立刻撤离！
Do you hear me?
听到了吗？
Get out of there, now!
离开那里 马上！
Base is clear, Prime.
基地已经清空了 擎天柱
Try not to wreck the joint.
尽量不要破坏设备
My thanks, Agent Fowler.
十分感谢 福勒探员
Bulkhead, are you holding up?
隔板 你还撑得住吗？
Any word... from Miko?
神子有什么消息吗？
Don't worry about her.
不用担心她
You need to focus on your own mission.
你得专注你自己的任务
Right. I... I need to... rest... just for a minute.
好吧 我得…休息…一小会儿
I know it's tough,
我知道这很难
but I need you to stay the course.
但我希望你能坚持到底
Bulkhead. Bulkhead! Bulkhead!
隔板 隔板 隔板？
Bulkhead! Answer me, you, rust bucket!
隔板 回答我 你这个生锈的水桶
I'm here, ranger.
我在呢 游骑兵
You had me scared two tonnes.
啊 你吓到我了 黑大个
I... I can't do it.
我…我做不到
I do not want to hear that kind of talk.
我不想听到这种话
Especially from the likes of you.
尤其不想从你这里听到
We both know you've made it through worse.
我们都知道 你经历过的艰难险阻
Down! Down!
趴下！趴下！
Not worse than this. Not even scraplets.
不会 不会比这更糟 连吸屑虫都…
Look, soldier,
听着 战士
you know as well as I do there is a mission...
你跟我一样清楚 这是个任务
... and the reason why you take the mission.
你清楚为什么要接手这个任务
Honor... duty...
荣誉…使命…
Family! Which is why you need  to do whatever it takes to finish this job...
家人！这才是原因
... and come home safely.
并且平安地回家
Miko, I am supposed to be protecting you.
神子 我的职责是保护你…
Bulkhead. I'm strapped tight inside ten tons of metal muscles.
隔板 我待在十吨重的钢筋铁骨里面
I am protected.
万无一失
Miko, check it out. New battle scars.
神子 来看看 新的战伤
Wow!
喔！
Miko?
神子？
I heaved on your floor mats. Sorry.
我吐在脚垫上了 抱歉
Before I became a warrior, I was a labourer.
我在成为战士之前 是个工人
I can build stuff, I can break stuff.
我能造东西 也能拆东西
I wanna be just like you, Bulk.
我想和你一样 小隔
No, you need to stop, now!
不 你必须立即住手
I can't, Bulk. I have to get you out of here...
不行 小隔 我必须救你出去！
Bulkhead, I know somewhere inside you always remember me.
隔板 我知道你内心的某个地方会一直记得我
And I just want you to know...
我只是想让你知道
I'll never forget you.
我永远也不会忘记你…
You're right, Fowler...
嗯 你是对的 福勒
I gotta dig deep... for the other bots... for Miko!
我必须坚持下去 为了其他的汽车人 为了神子！
There is no logic to his movements.
他的行动不合理
His trail is meant to lead us astray.
这些踪迹是用来误导我们的！
To find the Wrecker...
要找到救援队那小子
... we must not follow...
我们不能被牵着走
... we must anticipate.
要合理分析
Almost there.
哦 快到了
That's right, soldier.
好样的 战士
Dump that rock and come on home.
扔了那块石头 然后快回家!
Fowler. Miko, what is it?
我是福勒 什么事 神子？
What in Sam hill?
什么？
I'm in the middle of a crisis here and you want me to...
我这里正在紧要关头呢 你却要我…
Uh, put him on the line.
…让他接电话
Wrecker!
救援队小子！
Put down the rock and allow us to put you out of your misery.
放下那块石头 让我们来帮你解脱吧
Gotta swat some flies.
我得先拍死些苍蝇…
Fair warning.... I'm contagious.
警告你 这是会传染的！
Hold this.
帮我拿一会儿！
Mr. Vogel this is special Agent William Fowler of the United States government.
沃格先生 我是美国政府的特工威廉福勒
You are hereby deputized as an honorable Agent for the departement of...
你特此被任命为星际关系部的
... interstellar relations.
嗯…荣誉探员
Bulkhead, you still with me?
隔板 你还在吗？
I'm in the scrap and you put me on hold?
我这里危机四伏 你居然把我撂到一边了？
I want you to know...
我要告诉你
Miko safe, mission accomplished.
神子安然无恙 任务完成
That's my girl.
这才是我的好姑娘
Scurrydown,
躺好了
contact the warship for a containment unit.
联系战舰准备密闭容器
Bulkhead, do you read me?
隔板 能听到吗？
Ratchet, come here.
救护车 到这边来
Bulkhead, please respond!
隔板 请回话
The Iacon database?
铁堡数据库？
It's downloading into our mainframe.
它下载到我们的主机上来了！
Answer me, soldier!
回答我 战士！
Hahahahaha! Rafael, you are a genius!
哈哈哈 拉斐尔你真是个天才！
Will you keep it down?
你们能安静一下吗？
Your spark is mine, Wrecker.
你的火种是我的了 救援队小子
You want a taste of this? Do you?
想尝尝这个吗 嗯？
Catch!
接好了！
Fowler, mission accomplished.
福勒 任务完成
But you may have to... tuck me in.
看来你得 把我抱回去了
Raf, open the bridge! Now!
拉夫 打开环陆桥 快！
No!
不！